[
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The &ldquo;fairy&rdquo; type made it&rsquo;s debut in which generation of the Pokemon core series games?",
      "correct_answer": "6th",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2nd",
        "7th",
        "4th"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Who is the main heroine of the anime, Full Metal Panic!",
      "correct_answer": "Kaname Chidori",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Teletha Testarossa",
        "Melissa Mao",
        "Kyoko Tokiwa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Who is credited with having created the world&#039;s first video game Easter Egg?",
      "correct_answer": "Warren Robinett",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Julius Smith",
        "Will Crowther",
        "Don Woods"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Animals",
      "question": "What is the Gray Wolf&#039;s scientific name?",
      "correct_answer": "Canis Lupus",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Canis Aureus",
        "Canis Latrans",
        "Canis Lupus Lycaon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
      "question": "A comet&#039;s gaseous envelope (which creates the tail) is called what?",
      "correct_answer": "The coma",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The wake",
        "The backwash",
        "The ablative"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Super Mario and Paarthurnax (Skyrim) are voiced by the same actor.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "What was the name of the canceled projected by Blizzard Entertainment that would be later become Overwatch?",
      "correct_answer": "Titan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Omnic",
        "Omega",
        "Ghost"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "question": "Which car tire manufacturer is famous for its &quot;Eagle&quot; brand of tires, and is the official tire supplier of NASCAR?",
      "correct_answer": "Goodyear",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pirelli",
        "Bridgestone",
        "Michelin"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a word used to describe an earthquake?",
      "correct_answer": "Drop-slide",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Foreshock",
        "Strike-slip",
        "Temblor"
      ]
    }
  ]
